ride_name = "Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance"

questions = [
    {
        "question": "What year did Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance open at Disney's Hollywood Studios?",
        "answers": ["2019", "2018", "2020", "2021"],
        "correct_answer": "2019"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Disney World park is home to Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["Hollywood Studios", "Magic Kingdom", "Epcot", "Animal Kingdom"],
        "correct_answer": "Hollywood Studios"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the theme of Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["Star Wars", "Star Trek", "Guardians of the Galaxy", "Avatar"],
        "correct_answer": "Star Wars"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who designed Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["Walt Disney Imagineering", "Tony Baxter", "John Hench", "Bob Gurr"],
        "correct_answer": "Walt Disney Imagineering"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the height requirement to ride Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["40 inches", "38 inches", "44 inches", "48 inches"],
        "correct_answer": "40 inches"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the maximum speed of Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["8 mph", "10 mph", "12 mph", "15 mph"],
        "correct_answer": "8 mph"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the duration of the Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance ride?",
        "answers": ["18 minutes", "15 minutes", "20 minutes", "25 minutes"],
        "correct_answer": "18 minutes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of ride is Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["Trackless dark ride", "Roller coaster", "Simulated ride", "Boat ride"],
        "correct_answer": "Trackless dark ride"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Resistance base in Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["Black Spire Outpost", "Echo Base", "Yavin 4", "D'Qar"],
        "correct_answer": "Black Spire Outpost"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the main antagonist in Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["Kylo Ren", "Darth Vader", "Emperor Palpatine", "General Hux"],
        "correct_answer": "Kylo Ren"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the transport ship in Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["I-TS Transport", "Millennium Falcon", "X-Wing", "TIE Fighter"],
        "correct_answer": "I-TS Transport"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the pilot of the transport ship in Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["Lieutenant Bek", "Poe Dameron", "Finn", "Rey"],
        "correct_answer": "Lieutenant Bek"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the droid that assists you in Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["R5", "R2-D2", "BB-8", "C-3PO"],
        "correct_answer": "R5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Star Destroyer you are captured on in Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["Finalizer", "Executor", "Devastator", "Avenger"],
        "correct_answer": "Finalizer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Resistance leader who briefs you on your mission in Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["General Leia Organa", "Admiral Ackbar", "General Hux", "General Poe Dameron"],
        "correct_answer": "General Leia Organa"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the First Order officer who interrogates you in Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["General Hux", "Captain Phasma", "Kylo Ren", "Admiral Piett"],
        "correct_answer": "General Hux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the escape pod you use in Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["Escape Pod 1", "Escape Pod 2", "Escape Pod 3", "Escape Pod 4"],
        "correct_answer": "Escape Pod 1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Resistance pilot who helps you escape in Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["Poe Dameron", "Finn", "Rey", "Chewbacca"],
        "correct_answer": "Poe Dameron"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the planet you escape to in Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["Batuu", "Tatooine", "Endor", "Hoth"],
        "correct_answer": "Batuu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Resistance spy who helps you in Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance?",
        "answers": ["Vi Moradi", "Finn", "Rey", "Poe Dameron"],
        "correct_answer": "Vi Moradi"
    }
]